wallychamp.com 2016-04-03

# Privacy – WallyChamp

The following Privacy Policy covers WallyChamp.com which (“Wally Champ”, “Wally”, “we”, “us”, “our”). It is our goal to bring you information tailored to your personal interests but, at the same time, protect your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**By using WallyChamp.com, submitting information or using any of our products and services, you signify your acceptance of the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.**

This Privacy Policy covers Wally Champ's treatment of personal information that Wally Champ gathers when you are on the online sites and when you are using Wally Champ's services. Also, this Privacy Policy covers Wally Champ's treatment of any personal information that

Wally Champ's business partners share with us. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to and from the Wally Champ site as well as the practices of third parties that Wally Champ does not control or own, or individuals that Wally Champ does not employ or manage.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our Terms & Conditions (available at wallychamp.com/terms ). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and is part of, our Terms & Conditions.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time so check back often. Continued access of this website by you will constitute your acceptance of the changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

### 1\. Introduction

Thank you for visiting WallyChamp.com. This Privacy Policy is written to better explain how we collect and use your information. This Privacy Policy is a binding contract and you must agree to it to the same extent as our Terms & Conditions in order to use our services.

### 2\. Information You Provide to Us

The Online Sites generally collect personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. This includes but is not limited to when you register for our WALLYCHAMP.com Forum, enter a sweepstakes and complete a survey. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features such as posting on our forums.

Registration: In order to use select parts of our websites such as the WallyChamp.com Forum, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration forum, we require your email address and date of birth. Optional information such as your referrer or time zone may also be requested.

### 3\. Public Areas

When you contribute any content to a public area of the online sites such as our WallyChamp.com Forum or comments sections, the content you submit will be made available to the general public and will not be considered to be personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy. We recommend you use caution when submitting any sensitive information such as your full name, address, phone number, or other information that would allow users to locate you or information about you.

### 4\. Personal Information We Collect When You Buy from Us

In order for you to place an order with us, you must provide us your name, e-mail address, mailing address, date of birth, Paypal information and telephone number. We will not disclose any information that you provide to us except in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

### 5\. Automatic Information

Our servers may automatically collect information about your computer when you visit our website, including without limitation the website that referred you, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) and other usage and traffic information. Wally Champ uses this statistical information to analyze trends, gather demographic information and administer our websites so we may provide improved web experiences to our readers. The information is not collected in a manner that would identify you personally. We may provide statistical information, not personal information, to our partners about how our users, collectively use our websites. We may share this information with our partners, so that they may further understand the usage of their areas and our websites, so that they too can provide you with a better web experience. There may also be occasions when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose.

### 6\. Use of Information

We may use your information:

  * To enhance or improve user experience, Wally Champ or services.
  * To process transactions and sell, transfer, and exchange your information to a third party for their marketing purposes with no additional consent required from you.
  * To send e-mails about the site or respond to inquiries.
  * To send e-mails about our websites and other products, news, or updates for WallyChamp.com
  * To send e-mails about third parties’ products or services.
  * To identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our websites.
  * To enforce our Terms & Conditions.

### 7\. Cookies

In order to distinguish you from other users—especially other users on the same network as you— we need to use cookies to track your specific computer. Specifically, we use cookies to save your preferences, keep track of advertisements, and remember your shopping cart items. Additionally, our cookies may be accessible by third parties, or provided by third parties. For example, we may use Google AdSense on our websites, which uses the DoubleClick cookie to better target ads that you may find interesting or relevant. For these reasons we require that you keep cookies enabled when using our websites.

### 8\. Third Party Websites

WallyChamp.com may contain links to third party websites, advertisers or services that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party websites or services or their use of your personal information. If you access a third party website from our websites, you do so at your own risk and you understand that neither this Privacy Policy nor our Terms & Conditions apply to your use of such sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of any third party website or service that you visit.

### 9\. Third Party Access to Your Information

We do our best to protect your information from being accessed by third parties. However, since we may employ outside maintenance personnel or use a third party to host our material, there are third party entities which may have custody or access to your information. Because of this, it is necessary that you permit us to give access to your information to third parties to the same extent that you authorize us to do so. For greater certainty, every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you. Additionally, we may store your information or share it with certain other third parties for reasons that may or may not be related to maintenance, advertising, marketing, or other purposes related to our business. The following is a non-exhaustive list of other entities that we may store, share, or transfer your information with:

  * Google Analytics
  * Google AdSense
  * Parse.ly
  * ComScore
  * ChartBeat

### 10\. Marketing & Communication

When registering for a Wally Champ Forum or Wally Champ Store account, you will be given the option to opt-in to updates through the Wally Champ newsletter and the Wally Champ Store’s 'new in' and promotional emails. If you would prefer to opt-out from these e-mails, you can do so at any time by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the e-mail.

### 11\. Law Enforcement

We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either.

### 12\. Security of Information

We use SSL certificates to help secure the Wally Champ Site. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. You understand and agree that no transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It is in our interest to keep our websites secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

### 13\. California Online Privacy Protection Act

We are located in California and do permit California residents to access our websites and order from us. It is our intent to comply with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the act. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at wallychamp15@gmail.com with any questions.

### 14\. Amendments

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the amended version will be posted on our website in place of the old version. We will also include the date that the currently displayed Privacy Policy took effect to help you determine whether there have been any changes since you last used the website. The changes in this Privacy Policy become effective as soon as the changes are published to the website. If you continue to use the website after the changes become effective, it will signify your agreement to be bound by such modifications or revisions.

If you do not agree to the new Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using our service.

### 15\. Contact

Any inquiries about your rights under this Privacy Policy, or any other matters regarding your privacy, can be directed to wallychamp@gmail.com

**Last Updated Date: Aug 24th, 2015**
